[The Demon Master]
[Epsiode 1]
[Derui Wang Hua District]
[Sheng De College - Back To School]
I'm going to start
my university life alone here
An Chu Xia, fighting!
Missy, you're such miser
I'm going to collect
the scrap from your hostel
But you're asking me
to carry the baggage
So sorry
Well,
let me buy you a drink later
You're the only miser in this college
Look at them
Sis Nan Gong, your handbag is nice
I heard it's hard to get it
How could you get it?
So what?
That's right, you're Nan Gong
You...
What are you doing?
So sorry, I didn't mean it
Where are you coming from?
I'm a freshman here
Are you a freshman too?
How could Sheng De College
accept people like you?
That's right
People like me?
You came with a rag man's motorbike
It destroyed the image
of Sheng De College
Bro, let's go
Okay
See you later
Sis Nan Gong, she's carrying
the same handbag
I'm not a blind, you don't
have to remind me
Nan Gong Yin, how are you?
I've heard a lot about you
I'm Ming Yuan, a freshman
from Department of Design
What a coincidence!
You have a nice name
No, Nan Gong is more elegance
It seems we're still
charming like before
We could easily attract
people wherever we go
Come on, that's because
Shen Dong is absent today
Otherwise, everybody will stick to him
What a pup!
He's anxious
Han Qi Lu, don't come back
if you can't get Chu Xia
[The Demon Master]
[Episode 1]
[A month ago]
Qi Lu
It's abroad now and you
don't have to speed up
It's because of you
You said that you're hungry
I've eaten Curry Laksa
and Bak-kut-teh
And you're asking for fried banana now
I haven't eaten Nasi Lemak yet
Mind your words, naughty girl
I...
I'm going to speed up
How dare you get in my way?
Hello, can we make it on time?
Sure, it's not too late
Thank you
-Qi Lu!
-You're welcome
Let's take a photo together
Listen, I'll count
1, 2, 3
Qi Lu!
Qi Lu, don't scare me!
Help!
My boyfriend fell into the sea
Please save him!
Wait, you have to wear a life jacket
He'll die, please save him!
Dangerous!
Qi Lu!
An Chu Xia!
Will you marry me?
This is for you, surprise!
You told me,
proposal is the most
important moment for a girl
I bring you here as I didn't want
to miss the important moment
Qi Lu, thank you
This is Angel Coast
People said, the couples
who make a wish at here
before sunset on summer solstice
will live in happily forever
I, Han Qi Lu
only love An Chu Xia in my life
I'd like to live with An Chu Xia forever
I, An Chu Xia
only love Han Qi Lu in my life
I'd like to live with Han Qi Lu forever
On the engagement night
We should...
Good night
We should go to bed early
Why did you wear my cloth?
Don't be stingy, you
just have proposed to me
What about after marrying?
Are you okay?
Let's go
Are you alright?
I'll wash my eyes in the hotel
Take your time for shooting here
I'll look for you after this
Okay, the hotel is not too far from here
Come to me if you feel tired
Bye
Like it?
Long Island Iced Tea
Thank you
You're welcome
Long Island Iced Tea, please
I see
For you
So soon
Keep the count in the room 5000
Okay
Thank you
Where's my drink?
Your girlfriend just took it away
My girlfriend?
Hi, Jacky
You're arrived?
Okay, I'm coming right now
Hi, do you know his room number?
Chu Xia, don't be naughty
You have the access card
with you, just come in
Who is she?
Who are you?
I'm so sorry, I went to the wrong room
Han Qi Lu, don't you want
to let her go, do you?
I don't even know who is she
Do you think I'm naive? Don't lie
I never lie
How could she enter your room?
And she even took off her cloth
How could we stay together in the future
if you don't believe me?
Alright, I'll leave then
He didn't stop me
Hello, miss
Come drink with us
No money, thank you
Lady's free
Take a look
Lady's Night
Fine, just one, okay?
It's for you
Thank you
Okay
I'll stay for a while, you go first
See you tomorrow
See you
Bye
Hey babe! Are you okay?
No, thanks
You drink a lot, let me send you back
-Why not?
-Go
No
I'm a good man, I'll send you back
Okay
It might dangerous
for her to stay here alone
So heavy
Where are you going?
I miss you very much
Finally, you're here, I'm missing you
Why didn't you come to me?
Hold me tightly please
Don't you know how am I missing you?
Where are you going?
I miss you very much
An Chu Xia!
Who is this guy?
I don't know
Qi Lu, how did I get here?
Don't lie to me
No, I didn't
You don't believe that
the foreign lady has
nothing to do with me
So you're trying to revenge
on me with the guy
No, I didn't
Revenge?
Don't you think
I could be used easily?
Look at your face
You!
Stop it!
Why did you so stupid?
How could you take
a drink from a stranger?
The waiter served it to me
I didn't know it will happen
Are you a stupid?
Don't you know how many girls
was cheated because of it?
I'm a stupid and you're smart
Don't you know how
dangerous a lady walking alone?
When I was coming out from the hotel,
you didn't even go after me
It's obvious that
you're not caring of me
I was...
I was too angry at that time
Moreover,
I tried to look for you right after
Have you thought about it?
What if I was kidnapped?
Are you blaming me?
Did I chase you out?
You misunderstood that I was
having affair with the foreign lady
You're the one wanted to leave
Who asked for break-up?
I meant no point we stay together
if we don't believe each other
You're the one who asked for break-up
Alright, I'm the one who screwed it up
Did you care about my feeling
when you're holding
the foreign lady?
And you wronged me that
I was having affair with the guy
What are you doing?
I thought you knew about it
Where is your ring?
I was wearing it last night
It's just a small fight
How could you throw the ring?
You never take serious
for our engagement
That's great
Well, the God thinks that
we're not suitable for each other
An Chu Xia
Can't you be rational?
I thought it was just a small fight
and we could...
Let's break up
It's up to you